Finding Aid for Frank Dwight Fitzgerald papers, 1928-1944
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Frank Dwight Fitzgerald papers 1928-1944 1930-1939
Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.
851355 Aa 2; Ac
Michigan Secretary of State, 1931-1935; Governor of Michigan, 1935-1936 and 1939; and chairman, 1936, of the Michigan delegation to the Republican National Convention. Correspondence, speeches, press releases, newspaper clippings, and miscellaneous notebooks and printed materials concerning his political career.
28 linear feet
4 oversize volumes
1 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Judge and Mrs. John W. Fitzgerald (donor no. 4510 ). The bulk of the collection was received in 1969; the scrapbooks were received in 1993; additional material came in 2009.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Frank D. Fitzgerald, Republican governor of Michigan 1935-1936 and from January 1 to March 16, 1939, was born January 27, 1885 in Grand Ledge, Michigan. He attended Ferris Institute taking business courses but did not graduate. He began his career as post office clerk in Grand Ledge (his father was postmaster). He held this positions from 1906 to 1911. In 1912, he was elected as a Republican to the county board of supervisors. In addition, over the next several years Fitzgerald would hold a variety of positions in state government. In 1913, he became committee clerk in the Michigan State Senate. In 1915, he became a proof reader in the House of Representatives and in 1917 a bill clerk in the House.
During the period when the legislature was not in session, Fitzgerald sought other employment, one of these was as clerk in the office of Michigan Secretary of State. During World War I, he accepted the position of executive secretary of the Michigan Food Administration serving from 1917 to 1919. In 1919, he was chosen deputy secretary of state, but remained only a year to go into private business with an automobile dealership in Tennessee. The business did not flourish and Fitzgerald returned to Michigan accepting in 1923 the position of business manager in the Michigan State Highway Department.
In 1931, Fitzgerald was elected to the office of Michigan Secretary of State. During his tenure, Fitzgerald advocated the restructuring of the gas and weight taxes, and sought exemptions from the sales tax for products used in farm production and industrial manufacture. Although both were Republicans, Fitzgerald and Governor Wilber Brucker were at odds over several issues. In the election of 1932, Brucker went down to defeat to William A. Comstock while Fitzgerald was barely reelected in this decidedly Democratic year.
In 1934, Fitzgerald was elected governor of Michigan defeating Arthur Lacy who had defeated Governor Comstock in the primary. As governor, Fitzgerald called for a balanced budget and the need to streamline state government. In the 1936 Roosevelt landslide victory, Fitzgerald was defeated by Detroit mayor Frank Murphy. He returned to different business ventures but his real aim was to return to the governor's chair. Running on an anti-New Deal platform which contrasted his fiscal management with Murphy's, Fitzgerald defeated Murphy in 1938. He would served only a few weeks of his second term as he died March 16, 1939.
The Fitzgerald papers date from 1928 to 1944 but the bulk of the collection falls within the period of 1930 to 1939, the year of Fitzgerald's death. Papers dated after 1939 are those of his wife Queena. The collection primarily concerns the mechanics of campaigning for office with little documentation of the administration of either the office of secretary of state or governor. The collection has been arranged into seven series: Correspondence; Biographical / Personal; Photographs; Speeches and Press Releases; Political Career; National Republican Party published material; and Scrapbooks.
The largest series in the collection - Correspondence - is important for showing the range of Fitzgerald's political acquaintances and his skill in achieving elective office. A selective index to those who corresponded with Fitzgerald is appended to this finding aid.
Subjects:
Elections--Michigan--1932.; Elections--Michigan--1934.; Elections--Michigan--1936.; Elections--Michigan--1938.; Fitzgerald, Frank Dwight, 1885-1939.; Michigan--Politics and government--1929-1938.; Politicians--Michigan.; Presidents--United States--Election--1936.; Republican National Convention (21st: 1936: Cleveland, Ohio); Republican Party (Mich.); Governors--Michigan.; Michigan--Politics and government--1837-1950.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Billboards.; Handicapped persons.; Political elections--1936.
Contributors:
Abbott, Horatio J. (Horatio Johnson), 1876-1936; Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1876-1933.; Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1907-1967.; Atwood, Orville E., 1880-; Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.; Bennett, Harry Herbert, 1892-1979.; Bingay, Malcolm Wallace, 1884-; Blackney, William Wallace, 1876-1963.; Bohn, Frank Probasco, 1866-1944.; Bradley, Frederick Van Ness, 1898-1947.; Bridges, Styles, 1898-1961.; Briggs, Walter Owen, 1877-1952.; Brown, Prentiss M. (Prentiss Marsh), 1889-1973.; Brown, Walter Folger, 1869-1961.; Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.; Brumm, John Lewis, 1878-1958.; Cady, Burt D., 1874-; Cady, Claude Ernest, 1878-1953.; Carton, John J. (John Jay), 1856-1934.; Chapin, Roy D. (Roy Dikeman), 1880-1936.; Clancy, Robert Henry, 1882-1962.; Cleage, Albert B.; Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949.; Coughlin, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1891-1979.; Couzens, Frank, 1902-1950.; Couzens, James, 1872-1936.; Cramton, Louis C. (Louis Convers), b. 1875.; Crowley, David Henry, 1882-; Currie, Gilbert, 1882-1960.; Daniels, Josephus, 1862-1948.; Davidson, James Edward, 1867-; DeFoe, Murl Holcomb, 1879-; DeLand, Charles J., 1879-; Dempsey, Jack, 1895-1983.; Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.; Dillman, Grover C. (Grover Cleveland), 1889-1979; Dondero, George Anthony, 1883-1968.; Engel, Albert Joseph, 1888-1959.; Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.; Fry, Theodore I., 1881-; Fuller, George N. (George Newman), 1873-1957.; Fuller, Oramel B., b. 1858.; Green, Fred W. (Fred Warren), 1872-1936.; Groesbeck, Alexander J. (Alexander Joseph), 1873-1953.; Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.; Haber, William, 1899-1988.; Hannah, John A., 1902-1991; Hart, Michael James, 1877-1951.; Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.; Hooper, Joseph Lawrence, 1877-1934.; Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.; Hopkins, Harry L. (Harry Lloyd), 1890-1946.; Hubbard, Orville Liscum, 1903-1982.; Hull, Cordell, 1871-1955.; Hull, Ivan E., 1894-; James, William Francis, 1873-1945.; Jayne, Ira Waite, 1882-; Joslin, Theodore M.; Kellogg, John Harvey, 1852-1943.; Kelly, Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-1971.; Kennedy, G. Donald (George Donald), 1900-1988; Ketcham, John Clark, 1873-1941.; Kimball, Henry Mahlon, 1878-1935.; Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.; Lacy, Arthur J. (Arthur Jay), 1876-1975.; La Guardia, Fiorello H. (Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947.; Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-1987.; Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.; Lehr, John Camillus, 1878-1958.; Lorch, Emil, 1870-1963.; Louis, Joe, 1914-1981.; McKay, Frank D., 1883-; McLeod, Clarence John, 1895-1959.; McNitt, H. Earl, 1888-1944.; Maddy, Joseph E. (Joseph Edgar), 1891-1966.; Mapes, Carl Edgar, 1874-1939.; Martin, John Butlin, 1909-; Michener, Earl C. (Earl Cory), 1876-1957.; Moley, Raymond, 1886-1975.; Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.; Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.; O'Brien, Patrick H. (Patrick Henry), 1868-1959; O'Hara, John J., 1885-; Olds, Ransom Eli, 1864-1950.; Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860.; Perkins, Frances, 1880-1965.; Person, Seymour Howe, 1879-1957.; Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946.; Pollock, James K. (James Kerr), 1898-1968; Potter, William W., 1869-1940.; Read, Thomas, 1881-; Reichert, Rudolph Edward, 1887-1965.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.; Shafer, Paul W. (Paul Werntz), 1893-1954.; Shields, Edmund Claude, 1871-1947.; Sink, Charles A. (Charles Albert), 1879-1972.; Sloan, Alfred P. (Alfred Pritchard), 1875-1966.; Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.; Stack, John K., 1884-1935.; Toy, Harry Stanley, 1892-1955.; Tufty, Esther Van Wagoner, d. 1986.; Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.; Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-; Vaughan, Coleman C., 1857-; Walker, Louis Carlisle, 1875-1963.; Weideman, Carl May, 1898-1972.; White, Walter Francis, 1893-1955.; Wolcott, Jesse Paine, 1893-1969.; Woodruff, Roy Orchard, 1876-1953.; Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Correspondence
  - 1928-January 1931, 15 folders (Box 1)
  - February 1931-September 1931, 12 folders (Box 2)
  - October 1931-May 1932, 16 folders (Box 3)
  - June 1932-March 1933, 17 folders (Box 4)
  - April 1933-December 1933, 16 folders (Box 5)
  - January 1934-May 25, 1934, 19 folders (Box 6)
  - May 28, 1934-June 23, 1934, 18 folders (Box 7)
  - June 25, 1934-July 31, 1934, 18 folders (Box 8)
  - August 1, 1934-August 29, 1934, 19 folders (Box 9)
  - August 30, 1934-September 18, 1934, 15 folders (Box 10)
  - September 19, 1934-October 9, 1934, 17 folders (Box 11)
  - October 10, 1934-November 14, 1934, 19 folders (Box 12)
  - November 15, 1934-December 3, 1934, 20 folders (Box 13)
  - December 4, 1934-December 29, 1934, 24 folders (Box 14)
  - January 1935-November 1935, 16 folders (Box 15)
  - December 1935-March 1936, 16 folders (Box 16)
  - April 1936-July 1936, 24 folders (Box 17)
  - August 1936-October 10, 1936, 20 folders (Box 18)
  - October 11 1936-November 1936, 21 folders (Box 19)
  - December 1936 July 1938-March 1939, 13 folders (Box 20)
    (no correspondence for 1937 received)
  - Mrs. Fitzgerald correspondence
    - November 1939-1941 1943-1944, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Letters of condolence on the death of Governor Fitzgerald (Box 21)
- Biographical / Personal
  - Memorial tributes, resolutions, etc. 1939; also later biographical information, 2 volumes; 1 folders (Box 22)
  - Programs of events (Box 22)
- Photographs
  - Portraits (Box 22)
    (see also oversize folder)
  - FDF as governor (Box 22)
  - Political gatherings; campaign billboards (Box 22)
  - FDF with wife and son (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
- Speeches and press releases
  - Undated 1934-1939, 14 folders (Box 22)
- Political Career
  - Secretary of State: Legal brief, Standard Oil Company vs. Frank D. Fitzgerald, secretary of state of the state of Michigan undated (Box 22)
  - Gubernatorial Materials
    - Labor relations board and welfare (copies of bills, etc.) undated (Box 23)
    - Michigan Securities Commission 1934 (Box 23)
    - Public Trust Commission
      - General 1935 (Box 23)
      - Practices of members 1935 (Box 23)
    - Low number license plate distribution 1935, undated (Box 23)
    - Messages to the legislature
      - 1935 (Box 23)
      - 1936 1939 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
    - Petitions for pardons for individuals accused of violating injunction 1936 (Box 23)
    - Office manual for Genesee County Welfare Relief Commission 1936 (Box 23)
  - Campaign materials
    - Young Fitzgerald for Governor League of Michigan 1934 (Box 23)
    - Fitzgerald for Governor Clubs 1934 (Box 23)
    - Itineraries and schedules 1936 (Box 23)
    - Campaign biographies, flyers for meetings, and related materials 1936, 1938 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box 23)
    - Notebook concerning the Wayne County Fitzgerald organization 1934 (Box 23)
    - Notebook concerning the Fitzgerald for Governor Clubs 1934 (Box 23)
    - Nominating Petitions 1934 (Box 24)
    - Nominating Petitions 1934 (Box 25)
      (continued)
    - Nominating Petitions 1934 (Box 26)
    - Campaign newspapers (Folder 1)
- National Republican Party published material
  - Republican Party National Convention books 1924, 1936 (Box 27)
  - The Republican Reporter I-IV 1938 (Box 27)
  - The Republican Reporter V 1938 (Box 27)
  - Booklet: Quotations from Franklin Delano Roosevelt, 1938 (Box 27)
  - Booklet: Promise and Performance, 1938 (Box 27)
- Scrapbooks
  - 1924-1929, 2 folders (Box 27)
    (clippings and correspondence; the materials had originally been in a binder)
  - November 1928-September 1931 (Box 27)
  - September 1931-February 1933 (Box 27)
  - October 1933-August 1934 (Box 27)
  - March 1934-December 1936 (Volume 1)
  - May 1934-August 1934 (Volume 2)
  - January 1935-January 1936 (Volume 3)
  - January 1938-March 1939 (Volume 4)
  - Newspaper clippings 1934-1939, and loose materials from scrapbooks (Box 28)
Selective Index to Correspondents
Abbott, Horatio J. (Horatio Johnson), 1876-
Aug. 2, 1932, Aug. 10, 1933, Aug. 11, 1933, Apr. 27, 1936
Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1876-1933.
1932, 1933
Alger, Frederick Moulton, 1907-1967.
Nov. 21, 1934
Atwood, Orville E., 1880-
Apr. 9, 1930, Aug. 5, 1930, Aug. 8, 1930, Sept. 13, 1930, Aug. 13, 1931, Aug. 15, 1931, Aug. 16, 1931, 1936
Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.
Apr. 16, 1931
Bennett, Harry Herbert, 1892-1979.
June 28, 1932, June 30, 1932, Jan. 17, 1933, Feb. 5, 1934, May 18, 1934, Dec. 6, 1934, 1936
Bingay, Malcolm Wallace, 1884-
June 7, 1934, Aug. 1, 1934, Aug. 13, 1936
Blackney, William. Wallace, 1876-1963.
Nov. 30, 1934
Bohn, Frank Probasco, 1866-1944.
Oct. 25, 1929, Oct. 28, 1929, Dec. 26, 1929, 1930, Apr. 25, 1931, July 17, 1931, Oct. 21, 1931, 1932, Feb. 9, 1933, Nov. 2, 1933, Sept. 24, 1934
Bradley, Frederick Van Ness, 1898-1947.
Feb. 7, 1939
Bridges, Styles, 1898-1961.
Feb. 2, 1935, Mar. 2, 1935
Briggs, Walter Owen, 1877-1952.
Nov. 25, 1935, July 21, 1936
Brown, Prentiss Marsh, 1889-1973.
Aug. 15, 1935
Brown, Walter Folger, 1869-1961.
Mar. 15, 1932
Brucker, Wilber Marion, 1894-1968.
Apr. 23, 1930, May 5, 1930, Sept. 17, 1930, Nov. 18, 1930, July 10, 1931, Sept. 9, 1931, Nov. 5, 1931, Dec. 15, 1932, 1933, 1934, Oct. 18, 1936
Brumm, John Lewis, 1878-1928.
Mar. 11, 1936
Cady, Burt D., 1874-
May 29, 1930, June 2, 1930, Sept. 23, 1930, Oct. 4, 1930, Aug. 6, 1931, Sept. 24, 1931, May 11, 1932, May 12, 1932, Nov. 11, 1933, Jan. 8, 1934
Cady, Claude Ernest, 1878-1953.
Apr. 11, 1934
Carton, John J. (John Jay), 1856-1934.
Aug. 4, 1933
Chapin, Roy D. (Roy Dikeman), 1880-1936.
May 24, 1933, Nov. 13, 1933
Clancy, Robert Henry, 1882-1962
Nov. 19, 1931, Jan. 15, 1932, Mar. 22, 1932, June 22, 1932, July 19, 1932
Cleage, Albert B.
Nov. 2, 1936
Comstock, William Alfred, 1877-1949.
1934, July 25, 1935, Oct. 7, 1936, Nov. 9, 1936, Jan. 8, 1939, Jan. 19, 1939
Coughlin, Charles E. (Charles Edward), 1891-1979.
Sept. 24, 1936, Nov. 22, 1938
Couzens, Frank, 1902-1950.
Apr. 24, 1933, July 22, 1938
Couzens, James, 1872-1936.
Feb. 2, 1931, Mar. 18, 1931, Mar. 20, 1931, Mar. 6, 1933, Nov. 14, 1934, Nov. 30, 1934, Dec. 4, 1934, Nov. 19, 1935, Feb. 12, 1936, Sept. 18, 1936
Cramton, Louis C. (Louis Convers), b. 1875.
Sept. 21, 1934, Oct. 6, 1936
Crowley. David Henry, 1882-
Dec. 20, 1934, Oct. 15, 1936, Oct. 18, 1936, Nov. 16, 1936, Dec. 20, 1938
Currie, Gilbert, 1882-1960.
1929-1934
Daniels, Josephus, 1862-1948.
Feb. 25, 1935
Davidson, James Edward, 1867-
1929-1932, May 21, 1936, May 28, 1936, June 1, 1936, Aug. 4, 1936, Oct. 6, 1936, Nov. 9, 1936
DeFoe, Murl Holcomb, 1879-
1929-1934, 1936, July 22, 1938, Aug. 7, 1938, Feb. 21, 1939
DeLand, Charles J., 1879-
Oct. 31, 1929, Nov. 20, 1929, Sept. 30, 1930, Nov. 17, 1930, Dec. 30, 1930, May 18, 1931, Dec. 7, 1931, Aug. 5, 1932, Sept. 24, 1934, June 18, 1936, Sept. 24, 1936, Dec. 17, 1936
Dempsey, Jack, 1895-
Dec. 10, 1934, Feb. 1, 1935
Dickinson, Luren Dudley, 1859-1943.
May 15, 1930, June 4, 1930, 1931, 1934, Jan. 12, 1935, Oct. 18, 1938, Oct. 20, 1938
Dillman, Grover C., 1889-
Sept. 29, 1930, Nov. 6, 1930, 1931, Mar. 21, 1933, July 6, 1933, Aug. 30, 1933, Dec. 1, 1933, 1934, Aug. 12, 1935, Nov. 24, 1936, Feb. 8, 1939
Dondero, George Anthony, 1883-1968.
Dec. 20, 1934, June 27, 1935, July 2, 1936, Aug. 10, 1936, Sept. 23, 1936
Engel, Albert Joseph, 1888-1959.
1932-1936, Aug. 26, 1936
Ferguson, Homer, 1889-1982.
Jan. 5, 1932, Apr. 17, 1933, Sept. 24, 1934, Jan. 14, 1935
Fry, Theodore I., 1881-
May 24, 1934, July 3, 1934, July 16, 1934, Aug. 20, 1934, Nov. 8, 1934, Nov. 20, 1936, Jan. 26, 1939
Fuller, George N. (George Newman), 1873-1957.
Sept. 4, 1931, Dec. 18, 1933, Oct- 15, 1934, Nov. 12, 1936
Fuller, Oramel B., b. 1858.
Sept. 13, 1930, Dec. 30, 1930, May 19, 1932
Green, Fred Warren, 1872-1936.
Jan. 8, 1931, 1932-1934, Apr. 3, 1935, Nov. 24, 1936
Groesbeck, Alexander J., 1873-1953.
Dec. 26, 1930, Jan. 8, 1931, May 12, 1931, Nov. 25, 1931, 1932, Dec. 26, 1933, Jan. 12, 1934, Sept. 12, 1934, Sept. 25, 1934, Dec. 30, 1935, Jan. 23, 1939
Guest, Edgar A. (Edgar Albert), 1881-1959.
Oct. 1, 1931
Haber, William, 1899-1988.
Dec. 5, 1934, Dec. 6, 1934, Jan. 16, 1936, Oct. 8, 1936, Dec. 23, 1936
Hannah, John Alfred, 1902-
Oct. 17, 1935, Jan. 13, 1939
Hart, Michael James, 1877-1951.
July 29, 1932, Sept. 21, 1932
Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.
Dec. 13, 1929, Apr. 16, 1930, Apr. 19, 1930, Sept. 22, 1930, Mar. 2, 1931, Jan. 4, 1932, Mar. 28, 1932, Oct. 10, 1932, Oct. 18, 1932, 1934
Hooper, Joseph Lawrence, 1877-1934.
Oct. 24, 1929, Oct. 26, 1929, 1929-1931, May 26, 1932, May 28, 1932, Jan. 23, 1933, Mar. 4, 1933, Apr. 17, 1933
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.
Sept. 11, 1931, Feb. 27, 1939
Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972.
Dec. 19, 1934
Hopkins, Harry Lloyd, 1890-1946.
Dec. 4, 1934, Dec. 5, 1934
Hubbard, Orville Liscum, 1903-1982.
Nov. 27, 1933, Dec. 19, 1933, May 10, 1933, June 9, 1934, Aug. 16, 1934, Sept. 29, 1934, Oct. 1, 1934
Hull, Cordell, 1871-1955.
May 22, 1936
Hull, Ivan E., 1894-
Nov. 25, 1929, Jan. 7, 1930, Oct. 1, 1930, Apr. 7, 1931, May 18, 1931, Jan. 19, 1932, Mar. 1, 1932, Dec. 16, 1932, 1934-1936, Jan. 19, 1939
James, William Francis, 1873-1945.
Feb. 14, 1930, May 13, 1930, May 16, 1930, 1932, Aug. 25, 1933, 1934, Oct. 1, 1936, Oct. 8, 1936, Oct. 18, 1936
Jayne, Ira Waite, 1882-
Sept. 29, 1934
Joslin, Theodore M.
1929-1932, June 13, 1934, Aug. 2, 1934
Kellogg, John Harvey, 1852-1943
Oct. 19, 1936
Kelly, Harry F. (Harry Francis), 1895-1971.
June 2, 1933, Mar. 21, 1936, July 29, 1936
Kennedy, G. Donald (George Donald), 1900-
Dec. 29, 1936
Ketcham, John Clark, 1873-1941.
Mar. 14, 1931, July 21, 1932, July 27, 1932, Aug. 18, 1932, Jan. 25, 1933
Kimball, Henry Mahlon, 1878-1935.
May 13, 1935
Knox, Frank, 1874-1944.
June 18, 1936, Nov. 11, 1936, Dec. 4, 1935
Lacy, Arthur J. (Arthur Jay), 1876-1975.
Nov. 7, 1934
LaGuardia, Fiorello H. (Fiorello Henry), 1882-1947.
Apr. 6, 1936
Landon, Alfred M. (Alfred Mossman), 1887-1987.
May 22, 1936
Lawrence, Howard Cyrus, 1890-1961.
1930-1936, 1938, 1939
Lehr, John Camillus, 1878-1958.
May 17, 1934
Lorch, Emil, 1870-1963.
Dec. 17, 1934
Louis, Joe, 1914-1981.
July 5, 1935
McKay, Frank, 1883-1965.
Oct. 10, 1930, 1931, Feb. 18, 1932, Apr. 6, 1932, July 13, 1934, Nov. 14, 1934, 1936, Jan. 9, 1939, June 8, 1940
McLeod, Clarence John, 1895-1959.
Mar. 14, 1934
McNitt, H. Earl, 1888-1944.
May 23, 1932, Nov. 28, 1933, Nov. 19, 1934
Maddy, Joseph E. (Joseph Edgar), 1891-1966.
July 12, 1935, July 31, 1935, Aug. 13, 1936
Mapes, Carl Edgar, 1874-1939.
Nov. 15, 1933, Sept. 13, 1934, Dec. 12, 1934
Martin, John B., 1909-
July 13, 1934
Michener, Earl C. (Earl Cory), 1876-1957.
Oct. 6, 1930, Sept. 11, 1931, Oct. 23, 1931, Nov. 7, 1931, July 29, 1932, Sept. 16, 1932, Nov. 25, 1932, Nov. 21, 1934, Nov. 22, 1934, Nov. 26, 1934, Nov. 23, 1936
Moley, Raymond L., 1886-
Dec. 20, 1934
Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940.
Dec. 13, 1935
Murphy, Frank, 1890-1949.
Nov. 25, 1931, July 2, 1934, Nov. 24, 1936, Dec. 10, 1936, Nov. 9, 1938, Jan. 1, 1939, Jan. 13, 1939
O'Brien, Patrick Henry, 1868-
Aug. 25, 1933, Nov. 20, 1933, Jan. 18, 1934, Jan. 29, 1934, Oct. 7, 1936
O'Hara, John J., 1885-
Mar. 13, 1935, June 29, 1935, Aug. 1, 1935
Olds, Ransom Eli, 1864-1950.
June 29, 1936
Osborn, Chase S. (Chase Salmon), b. 1860.
1930, July 24, 1931, Sept. 10, 1931, May 22, 1933, Dec. 4, 1933, 1934-1936, Oct. 18, 1938, Feb. 1, 1939
Perkins, Frances, 1882-1965.
Sept. 24, 1935, Oct- 11, 1936, Dec. 8, 1938, Dec. 2, 1938
Person, Seymour Howe, 1879-1957.
1931, 1932
Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946.
Oct. 21, 1931
Pollock, James Kerr, 1898-1968.
May 18, 1936, June 19, 1936
Potter, William W., 1869-1940.
Oct. 2, 1934, Oct. 3, 1934, Dec. 26, 1934, Dec. 27, 1934
Read, Thomas, 1881-
Sept. 10, 1936, Sept. 30, 1936
Reichert, Rudolph Edward, 1887-1965
Nov. 24, 1936
Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.
June 4, 1935, June 7, 1935
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-1971.
Nov. 13, 1930, Nov. 30, 1934, Dec. 13, 1934, June 11, 1935, Nov. 26, 1935, Feb. 16, 1939
Shafer, Paul Werntz, 1893-1954.
Feb. 6, 1939
Shields, Edmund Claude, 1871-1947.
July 28, 1936
Sink, Charles Albert, 1879-1972.
Aug. 31, 1936
Sloan, Alfred Pritchard, 1875-1966.
Nov. 23, 1938
Smith, Shirley Wheeler, 1875-1959.
June 14, 1934, Feb. 12, 1936, Nov. 12, 1936
Stack, John K., 1884-1935.
Sept. 21, 1933, Mar. 8, 1934, Apr. 10, 1934, May 8, 1934, May 17, 1934, June 22, 1934, Aug. 20, 1934, Nov. 8, 1934
Toy, Harry Stanley, 1892-
Sept. 30, 1930, May 15, 1931, Dec. 12, 1932, May 8, 1933, June 5, 1934, Sept. 18, 1934, Nov. 7, 1934
Tufty, Esther Van Wagoner, d. 1986.
Nov. 21, 1938
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
Dec. 16, 1930, Feb. 2, 1931, Aug. 15, 1932, 1933-1935, Mar. 21, 1936, Apr. 27, 1936, Sept. 24, 1936, Nov. 9, 1936, Jan. 7, 1939
Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-
1934, Dec. 20, 1935, Dec. 23, 1935, June 17, 1936, Aug. 20, 1936
Vaughan, Coleman C., b. 1857.
Apr. 9, 1930, Sept. 4, 1931, Aug. 18, 1933, Mar. 31, 1934, Dec. 11, 1934
Walker, Louis Carlisle, 1875-1963.
Aug. 27, 1934, May 18, 1936, July 2, 1936, Oct. 13, 1936, Nov. 30, 1936
Weideman, Carl May, 1898-1972.
Jan. 22, 1934
White, Walter Francis, 1893-1955.
Dec. 14, 1934
Wolcott, Jesse Paine, 1893-1969.
Aug. 13, 1931, May 2, 1932, May 10, 1932, 1934, Jan. 15, 1935, May 8, 1935, Sept. 8, 1936
Woodruff, Roy Orchard, 1876-1953.
Nov. 26, 1929, 1930-1934, Aug. 6, 1935
Yost, Fielding Harris, 1871-1946.
Oct. 26, 1934